<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Volleyball</string>

    <!--Common Terminologies-->
    <string name="term1">Ace</string>
    <string name="term2">Assist</string>
    <string name="term3">Attack</string>
    <string name="term4">Attacker</string>
    <string name="term5">Attack Block</string>
    <string name="term6">Attack Error</string>
    <string name="term7">Attack Line</string>
    <string name="term8">Back Row/Court</string>
    <string name="term9">Back Row Attack</string>
    <string name="term10">Back Set</string>
    <string name="term11">Baseline</string>
    <string name="term12">Block</string>
    <string name="term13">Blocking Error</string>
    <string name="term14">Center Line</string>
    <string name="term15">Closing the Block</string>
    <string name="term16">“Cover”: </string>
    <string name="term17">Cross-Court Attack</string>
    <string name="term18">Cut Shot</string>
    <string name="term19">Defense</string>
    <string name="term20">Dink</string>
    <string name="term21">Double Block</string>
    <string name="term22">Double Hit</string>
    <string name="term23">Down Ball</string>
    <string name="term24">Five-One (5-1)</string>
    <string name="term25">Floater</string>
    <string name="term26">Forearm Pass</string>
    <string name="term27">Four-Two (4-2)</string>
    <string name="term28">Free ball</string>
    <string name="term29">Game Plan</string>
    <string name="term30">Held ball</string>
    <string name="term31">Hitter</string>
    <string name="term32">Hitting percentage</string>
    <string name="term33">Joust</string>
    <string name="term34">Jump serve</string>
    <string name="term35">Key player/play</string>
    <string name="term36">Kill</string>
    <string name="term37">Libero</string>
    <string name="term38">Lineup</string>
    <string name="term39">Line serve</string>
    <string name="term40">Line shot</string>
    <string name="term41">Load</string>
    <string name="term42">Middle back</string>
    <string name="term43">Middle blocker</string>
    <string name="term44">Mintonette</string>
    <string name="term45">Net Height</string>
    <string name="term46">Off-blocker</string>
    <string name="term47">Off-Speed Shots</string>
    <string name="term48">Outside Hitter</string>
    <string name="term49">Overhand Pass</string>
    <string name="term50">Overhand Serve</string>
    <string name="term51">Pass</string>
    <string name="term52">Pancake</string>
    <string name="term53">Party ball</string>
    <string name="term54">Pipe</string>
    <string name="term55">Play</string>
    <string name="term56">Quick Set</string>
    <string name="term57">Rally Scoring</string>
    <string name="term58">Ready position</string>
    <string name="term59">Red Card</string>
    <string name="term60">Rotation</string>
    <string name="term61">Seam</string>
    <string name="term62">Serve</string>
    <string name="term63">Set Attack</string>
    <string name="term64">Spike</string>
    <string name="term65">Substitution</string>
    <string name="term66">Tandem</string>
    <string name="term67">Three-meter Line</string>
    <string name="term68">Tool</string>
    <string name="term69">Touch</string>
    <string name="term70">Transition</string>
    <string name="term71">Triple-block</string>
    <string name="term72">Underhand serve</string>
    <string name="term73">Wipe</string>
    <string name="term74">W serve-receive formation</string>
    <string name="term75">Yellow Card</string>


    <!--Definition-->
    <string name="term1_definition"> A serve that results directly in a point, either when the ball hits the floor on the receiving team’s side of the court untouched or is touched but unable to be kept in play by the receiving team.</string>
    <string name="term2_definition"> When a player sets, passes or digs the ball directly to a teammate who attacks the ball and gets a kill.</string>
    <string name="term3_definition"> The action of attempting to hit the ball onto the opponents side of the court. Types of attacks include a spike, tip, roll shot and dump.</string>
    <string name="term4_definition"> Also "hitter" and "spiker." A player who attempts to hit a ball offensively with the purpose of terminating play.</string>
    <string name="term5_definition"> The defensive teams attempt to block a spiked ball.</string>
    <string name="term6_definition"> An attack botched in one of 5 ways: Ball lands out of bounds; ball goes into net; attacker commits center line or net violation, or attacker illegally contacts ball. Getting blocked can also be considered an attack error.</string>
    <string name="term7_definition"> A line 3 meters (10 feet) away from, and parallel to, the net. Separates the front-row players from the back row players. A back row player cannot legally attack the ball above the net unless he takes off from behind the attack line.</string>
    <string name="term8_definition"> Space from baseline (end line) to attack line. There are 3 players whose court positions are in this area (positions 1, 6 and 5 on court).</string>
    <string name="term9_definition"> When a back row player takes off from behind the attack line (10-foot/3-meter) line and attacks the ball. Various terms for back row attacks include "A," "B," "C," "D," "Pipe" and "Bic".</string>
    <string name="term10_definition"> A set delivered to a hitter behind the setter.</string>
    <string name="term11_definition"> The back boundary of the court. Also called the end line.</string>
    <string name="term12_definition"> One of the six basic skills. A defensive play by one or more front-row players meant to intercept a spiked ball. The combination of one, two or three players jumping in front of the opposing spiker and contacting the spiked ball with the hands.</string>
    <string name="term13_definition"> Touching the net, crossing the centerline, blocking a set or serve or any other “local” violation that occurs while making a block attempt.</string>
    <string name="term14_definition"> The boundary that runs under the net and divides the court into two equal halves.</string>
    <string name="term15_definition"> The responsibility of the assisting blocker(s) to angle their body relative to the first blocker.</string>
    <string name="term16_definition"> Refers to the hitter having his/her teammates ready to retrieve rebounds from the opposing blockers.</string>
    <string name="term17_definition"> An attack directed diagonally from the point of attack. Also called an angle hit.</string>
    <string name="term18_definition"> A spike from the hitter’s strong side that travels at a sharp angle across the net.</string>
    <string name="term19_definition"> One of the 6 basic skills. The key skills used to receive the opponents attack are digging and sprawling. The dig resembles a forearm pass from a low ready position and is used more for balls that are hit near the defender. </string>
    <string name="term20_definition"> A one-handed, soft hit into the opponent’s court using the fingertips. Also called a tip.</string>
    <string name="term21_definition"> Two players working in unison to intercept a ball at the net.</string>
    <string name="term22_definition"> Violation. Two successive hits by the same player.</string>
    <string name="term23_definition"> Type of attack. “Down” refers to the blockers who neither jump, nor raise their hands above the net.</string>
    <string name="term24_definition"> An offensive system that uses five hitters and one setter.</string>
    <string name="term25_definition"> A serve with no spin so the ball follows an erratic path.</string>
    <string name="term26_definition"> Sometimes referred to as the “pass,” “bump” or “dig”.</string>
    <string name="term27_definition"> An offensive system using four hitters and two setters.</string>
    <string name="term28_definition"> Returning the ball to the opponent without the intent to get a kill. Usually a slow, arcing pass or “roll” shot rather than a spike.</string>
    <string name="term29_definition"> Offensive and defensive emphasis for an opponent. Usually organized for each rotation by the coaching staff.</string>
    <string name="term30_definition"> A ball that comes to rest during contact resulting in a violation.</string>
    <string name="term31_definition"> Also “spiker” or “attacker.” The player who is responsible for hitting the ball.</string>
    <string name="term32_definition"> A statistic derived from total kills minus total attack errors, divided by total attempts.</string>
    <string name="term33_definition"> When 2 opposing players contact the ball simultaneously above the net causing the ball to momentarily come to rest; the point is replayed if this is called by the official.</string>
    <string name="term34_definition">  The server uses an approach, toss, takeoff and serves the ball with a spiking motion while in the air. There are two main types: jump float, jump spin.</string>
    <string name="term35_definition"> To discern a team’s best player or probable next play by observation of patterns or habits.</string>
    <string name="term36_definition"> An attack that results directly in a point or side out.</string>
    <string name="term37_definition"> A player specialized in defensive skills. This player must wear a contrasting jersey color from his or her teammates and cannot block or attack the ball when it is entirely above net height. </string>
    <string name="term38_definition"> Players starting rotation and, therefore, serving order. Numbered 1,2,3,4,5,6.</string>
    <string name="term39_definition"> A straight-ahead serve landing near the opponent’s left sideline.</string>
    <string name="term40_definition"> A ball spiked along an opponent’s sideline, closest to the hitter and outside the block.</string>
    <string name="term41_definition"> Body position for the blockers so that they are most effective.</string>
    <string name="term42_definition"> A defensive system that uses the middle back player in 6 to cover deep spikes. Also called “6 back” defense.</string>
    <string name="term43_definition"> Usually plays in the middle of the net when in the front row and moves laterally to her blocking assignments.</string>
    <string name="term44_definition"> The original name of the game of volleyball, created by William Morgan.</string>
    <string name="term45_definition"> Women - 7 feet, 4-1/8 inches high (2.24m). Men – 7 feet, 11-5/8 inches high (2.43m).</string>
    <string name="term46_definition"> Outside blocker not included in the double block. Also called off-side blocker.</string>
    <string name="term47_definition">  An attack that is intentionally slow. Ball spiked with less than maximum force but with spin. Also called “roll” shot.</string>
    <string name="term48_definition"> Usually plays at the ends of the net when in the front row. Also called right-side (opposite) or left side (power).</string>
    <string name="term49_definition"> A pass with both hands open that is controlled by the fingers, with the face below the ball. Both hands simultaneously contact the ball above the head and direct it to the intended target.</string>
    <string name="term50_definition"> Serving the ball and striking it with the hand above the shoulder. Float or spin.</string>
    <string name="term51_definition"> One of the 6 basic skills. Receiving a serve or the first contact of the ball with the intent to control the ball to another player. Also called a “bump”.</string>
    <string name="term52_definition"> One-hand floor defensive technique where the hand is extended and slid along the floor palm down while the player dives or extension rolls so the ball bounces off the back of the hand and is considered legal.</string>
    <string name="term53_definition"> When the ball is passed across the net in front of the attack line so the front-row attacker can immediately hit the ball on the first contact.</string>
    <string name="term54_definition"> A back row attack from the middle of the court. Position 6.</string>
    <string name="term55_definition">An attack with a planned fake, usually including 2 or more hitter.</string>
    <string name="term56_definition"> An extremely low vertical set used to beat the opponent’s block. Can be set at any position on the net.</string>
    <string name="term57_definition"> Scoring method where points can be won by the serving or receiving team.</string>
    <string name="term58_definition">  The flexed, yet comfortable, posture a player assumes before moving to the point of contact.</string>
    <string name="term59_definition"> Given by the official to a player or coach for flagrant misconduct resulting in a point/side out to the opponent. Results in automatic ejection and a point/side out for the opponent.</string>
    <string name="term60_definition"> The clockwise movement of players around the court and through the serving position following a side out. Players must retain their initial rotational order throughout the entire game, but once the ball is contacted on serve they are allowed to move anywhere.</string>
    <string name="term61_definition"> The midpoint between 2 players.</string>
    <string name="term62_definition"> The tactical skill in which a ball is directed to a point where a player can spike it into the opponent’s court. Sets can be set at different heights and different locations on the net and offensively there are names for each of these. </string>
    <string name="term63_definition"> When a setter attempts to score rather than set the ball to a setter. Also called a shoot set. </string>
    <string name="term64_definition"> Also called a hit or attack. A ball contacted with force by a player on the offensive team who intends to terminate the ball on the opponent’s floor or off the opponent’s blocker.</string>
    <string name="term65_definition"> Allows one player to replace another player already on the court. Rules dictate the number of subs each team is allowed.</string>
    <string name="term66_definition"> A combination in which one player attacks immediately behind another.</string>
    <string name="term67_definition">  The line extended across the court to signify the point which a back row player must leave the ground behind to attack the ball. Also called the "attack line” and "10-foot line."</string>
    <string name="term68_definition"> When an attacker hits the ball off an opposing blocker’s arms out of bounds. Also called a wipe.</string>
    <string name="term69_definition"> A player contacting the ball on the defensive play.</string>
    <string name="term70_definition"> To switch from offense to defense and vice versa.</string>
    <string name="term71_definition">  Block formed by all 3 front-row players.</string>
    <string name="term72_definition"> A serve performed with an underhand striking action. The ball is usually contacted with the heel of the hand.</string>
    <string name="term73_definition"> To deliberately spike the ball off an opponent’s hands and out of bounds. Also called a tool.</string>
    <string name="term74_definition"> Three players in the front row, two in the back.</string>
    <string name="term75_definition"> Given by the official to a player or coach as a warning of misconduct. Two yellow cards result in an automatic red card.</string>

</resources>